(Sheldon:)I didn't say that.
But no, I don't.
(Penny:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Penny,
where do I begin?
(Sheldon:)The simple-mindedness
of your idea
(Sheldon:)is exceeded only by its
crass consumerism and banality.
(Penny:)And Leonard didn't want
to work with you?
(Penny:)Imagine that.
(Sheldon:)I know, it's baffling.
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ The trouble I've seen... ♪
(Penny:)Sheldon, I'm gonna
make some cocoa.
(Penny:)Do you want some?
(Sheldon:)Do you make it
with milk or water?
(Sheldon:)- Milk.
- Real cocoa?
(Penny:)That's what it says
on the packet.
(Sheldon:)Do you have
those little marshmallows?
(Penny:)No, sorry.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose
it's appropriate.
(Penny:)What does that mean?
(Sheldon:)A disappointing drink
for a disappointing day.
(Raj:)Hey, look at this.
(Raj:)20 people from the university
have already signed up
(Raj:)for our private beta.
(Leonard:)I'm telling you,
(Leonard:)the Lenwoloppali
Differential Equation Scanner
(Leonard:)meets a real need.
We've got a hit.
(Raj:)What do you think we
should sell it for?